{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946901801019","data":{"timestamp":" 946901801019"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_151604"," gameId":" ea24a757-3726-4e3e-8104-af24f6f48486"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_43"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nani_nani-huu-joto-gani"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" nani"," userResponse":" gani"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946901804280","data":{"timestamp":" 946901804280"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_151604"," gameId":" ea24a757-3726-4e3e-8104-af24f6f48486"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_43"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nani_nani-huu-joto-gani"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" nani"," userResponse":" joto"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946901807533","data":{"timestamp":" 946901807533"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_151604"," gameId":" ea24a757-3726-4e3e-8104-af24f6f48486"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_43"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nani_nani-huu-joto-gani"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" nani"," userResponse":" nani"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946901829226","data":{"timestamp":" 946901829226"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_151604"," gameId":" ea24a757-3726-4e3e-8104-af24f6f48486"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_43"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nani_je-hiki-ghafla-nani"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" nani"," userResponse":" je"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946901832607","data":{"timestamp":" 946901832606"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_151604"," gameId":" ea24a757-3726-4e3e-8104-af24f6f48486"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_43"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nani_je-hiki-ghafla-nani"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" nani"," userResponse":" hiki"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946901835519","data":{"timestamp":" 946901835519"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_151604"," gameId":" ea24a757-3726-4e3e-8104-af24f6f48486"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_43"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nani_je-hiki-ghafla-nani"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" nani"," userResponse":" nani"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946901863272","data":{"timestamp":" 946901863272"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_151604"," gameId":" ea24a757-3726-4e3e-8104-af24f6f48486"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_43"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" gari_mkono-vya-gari-pumzi"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" gari"," userResponse":" vya"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946901866551","data":{"timestamp":" 946901866551"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_151604"," gameId":" ea24a757-3726-4e3e-8104-af24f6f48486"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_43"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" gari_mkono-vya-gari-pumzi"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" gari"," userResponse":" mkono"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946901869549","data":{"timestamp":" 946901869549"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_151604"," gameId":" ea24a757-3726-4e3e-8104-af24f6f48486"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_43"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" gari_mkono-vya-gari-pumzi"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" gari"," userResponse":" pumzi"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946901875384","data":{"timestamp":" 946901875384"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_151604"," gameId":" ea24a757-3726-4e3e-8104-af24f6f48486"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_43"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" gari_mkono-vya-gari-pumzi"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" gari"," userResponse":" gari"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946901891186","data":{"timestamp":" 946901891185"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_151604"," gameId":" ea24a757-3726-4e3e-8104-af24f6f48486"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_43"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" gari_mkono-vya-gari-pumzi"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946901891283","data":{"timestamp":" 946901891283"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_151604"," gameId":" ea24a757-3726-4e3e-8104-af24f6f48486"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_43"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Naweza kutulia na kukifurahia kitabu mimi ____________!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ____________"," userResponse":" MWENYEWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946901956719","data":{"timestamp":" 946901956719"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_151604"," gameId":" d41a32a1-3001-4f2f-b6e5-2b6dc8dc1034"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Vayu ____________!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ____________"," userResponse":" UPEPO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946902027757","data":{"timestamp":" 946902027757"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_151604"," gameId":" 3f616d7d-a23a-459b-b2c0-3beebff3c87e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" upepo_mno-baba-baridi-upepo"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" upepo"," userResponse":" baba"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946902032835","data":{"timestamp":" 946902032835"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_151604"," gameId":" 3f616d7d-a23a-459b-b2c0-3beebff3c87e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" upepo_mno-baba-baridi-upepo"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" upepo"," userResponse":" mno"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946902037802","data":{"timestamp":" 946902037802"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_151604"," gameId":" 3f616d7d-a23a-459b-b2c0-3beebff3c87e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" upepo_mno-baba-baridi-upepo"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" upepo"," userResponse":" upepo"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946902069843","data":{"timestamp":" 946902069843"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_151604"," gameId":" 3f616d7d-a23a-459b-b2c0-3beebff3c87e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" upepo_jua-punde-jua-upepo"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" upepo"," userResponse":" upepo"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946902100946","data":{"timestamp":" 946902100946"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_151604"," gameId":" 3f616d7d-a23a-459b-b2c0-3beebff3c87e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" upepo_baba-panya-upepo-hata"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" upepo"," userResponse":" upepo"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946902135156","data":{"timestamp":" 946902135156"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_151604"," gameId":" 3f616d7d-a23a-459b-b2c0-3beebff3c87e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" upepo_baba-hadithi-upepo-kwani"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" upepo"," userResponse":" upepo"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946902168786","data":{"timestamp":" 946902168786"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_151604"," gameId":" 3f616d7d-a23a-459b-b2c0-3beebff3c87e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" upepo_upepo-baridi-baridi-punde"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" upepo"," userResponse":" punde"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946902172663","data":{"timestamp":" 946902172663"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_151604"," gameId":" 3f616d7d-a23a-459b-b2c0-3beebff3c87e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" upepo_upepo-baridi-baridi-punde"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" upepo"," userResponse":" upepo"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946902212864","data":{"timestamp":" 946902212864"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_151604"," gameId":" 3f616d7d-a23a-459b-b2c0-3beebff3c87e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" upepo_baba-shule-upepo-nani"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" upepo"," userResponse":" upepo"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946902287556","data":{"timestamp":" 946902287555"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_151604"," gameId":" 3f616d7d-a23a-459b-b2c0-3beebff3c87e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" upepo_baba-shule-upepo-nani"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946902287661","data":{"timestamp":" 946902287661"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_151604"," gameId":" 3f616d7d-a23a-459b-b2c0-3beebff3c87e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni ____________!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ____________"," userResponse":" UPEPO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}